{
    "questions" : [
        {
            "question" : "The correct order of servlet life cycle is",
            "choices" : [
                "Instantiation, Initialization, Request Handling, Destruction",
                "Instantiation, Initialization, Request Handling, Release",
                "Instantiation, Initialization, Response, Release",
                "Instantiation, Initialization, Response, Destruction"
            ],
            "answer" : "a1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "This object can be used to get configuration information from the web.xml file.",
            "choices" : [
                "ServletContext object ",
                "HttpServletResponse object",
                "HttpServletRequest object",
                "Session object"
            ],
            "answer" : "b1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is the right tag to write PHP?",
            "choices" : [
                "<% %>",
                "<php> </php>",
                "<?php ?>",
                "<script type=”php”> </script>"
            ],
            "answer" : "c3"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is true about an include and require in PHP?",
            "choices" : [
                "Include only includes the HTML in the file, while require includes the PHP code too.",
                "Require only includes the HTML in the file, while include imports the HTML and PHP code.",
                "Require will stop executing as soon as an error is reached, and include will continue executing the code after the error. ",
                "Include will stop executing as soon as an error is reached, and require will continue executing the code after the error."
            ],
            "answer" : "d3"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Valid syntax to write a for loop",
            "choices" : [
                "for($i < 5; $i = 0;)",
                "for($i = 0; $i < 5; $i++)",
                "for($i < 5;)",
                "for( $i < 5; $i = 0; $i++)"
            ],
            "answer" : "e2"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is the right syntax in creating an array in PHP?",
            "choices" : [
                "$myArray = new array();",
                "$myArray = Array.create();",
                "$myArray = array();",
                "$myArray = create(array);"
            ],
            "answer" : "f3"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following shows the right syntax in implementing a file system in Node.js.",
            "choices" : [
                "var filesystem = require(‘fs’);",
                "var filesystem = include(‘fs’);",
                "$filesystem = require(‘fs’);",
                "$filesystem = include(‘fs’);"
            ],
            "answer" : "g1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "This is an event triggered when an EventEmitter faces an error in Node.js.",
            "choices" : [
                "try-catch event",
                "error event",
                "event listener",
                "error listener"
            ],
            "answer" : "h2"
        },
        {
            "question" : "The following are functionalities of Node Package Manager (NPM) except one:",
            "choices" : [
                "Node.js packages and modules available via online repositories",
                "Utility to install packages using a machines command line, also it can do version management and Node.js packages’ independency management.",
                "initiates all variables, declares functions and waits for an event to occur. "
            ],
            "answer" : "i3"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is the common syntax of a JSP tag?",
            "choices" : [
                "<% %>",
                "<?  ?>",
                "<%JSP  %>",
                "<JSP>  </JSP>"
            ],
            "answer" : "j1"
        }
    ]
}